Delusion​
Sentiment​
Compensation​
Federation​
Delusion Sentiment
Compensation Federation​
Vocal: Kotone​
Art: Bachiko​
Video: Itoh Igusa​
​ I went and said it​
​ I went and said it ​​
Video: Itoh Igusa​
​ I went and said it​
​ I went and said it ​​
Video: Itoh Igusa​
​ I went and said it​
​ I went and said it ​​
Video: Itoh Igusa​
​ I went and said it​
​ I went and said it ​​
​​ I want to be with you​
​ I want to be with you ​​
​​ just one more time​
​ just one more time ​​
.​
​ No, no, to drag things out​
​  No, no, to drag things out  ​​
​ would be annoying​
​ would be annoying ​​
.​
​ I’m sorry, ​​
​ come back ​​
Carbon dioxide​
​ I’m sorry, ​​
​ come back ​​
Carb​​on dioxi​de​
your atmosp​​heric co​ncentration​
your at​​mo​spheric conc​entration​
​ I’m sorry, ​​
your at​​mo​spheric conce​ntration​
your atmospheric conce​​ntr​ation​
​ I’m sorry, ​​
your atmospheric concentration​
I want to soak in​
a dream of a swamp​
Even ​​if you​
E​​ven if you​
Even if you​
Even ​​if you​
tell m​​e I'm​
t​​ell me I'm​
tell me I'm​
tell me I'​​m​
selfish, I'l​​l​
tell m​​e I'm​
selfis​​h, I'll​
y​​ou tell me​
s​​elfish, I'll​
selfish, I'll​
selfish, I'l​​l​
selfis​​h, I'll​
just la​​p it up​
s​​elfish, I'll​
ju​​st lap it up​
just lap it up​
​​ It’s not uncertain​
​ It’s not uncertain ​​
​​ there’s no future​
​ there’s no future ​​
​​I want to be reborn with your face​
​  I want to be reborn with your face  ​​
​​ I went and found out​
​ I went and found out ​​
​​Even if you flip over the words “I hate you”​
​  Even if you flip over the words “I hate you”  ​​
​​There’s no “I love you” hidden there​
​  There’s no “I love you” hidden there  ​​
​​I want these emotions​
​ I want these emotions ​​
​ to be fulfilled​
​ to be fulfilled ​​
Depending on others too much,
growing fat, they circulate through my heart​
​ to be fulfilled​
​ to be fulfilled ​​
Depending on others too much,
growing fat, they circulate through my heart​
​ to be fulfilled​
​ to be fulfilled ​​
Depending on others too much,
growing fat, they circulate through my heart​
​ to be fulfilled​
​ to be fulfilled ​​
Depending on others too much,
growing fat, they circulate through my heart​
Let’s adopt the slogan “Slim Down Fat Emotions”​
It’ll be like when we first met​
​ I’m mad with idealism,​
​  I’m mad with idealism,  ​​
​ imagining a smile​
​ imagining a smile ​​
My bloodshot​
wish will​
soon be​
relieved​
But​
there’s no love anywhere​
that’s “just fine”​
So​
Delusion​
Sentiment​
Compensation​
Federation​
Embraced love and​
shouted out their ideals​
A melody of fools​
with nowhere to go​
Retrying​
Rebirth​
​Teleportation​
​Teleportation​​
The ​​number​
The number​
The number of tries
keeps accumulating​
At the mercy of an endless love​
The number of tries
keeps accumulating​
At the mercy of an endless love​
The number of tries
keeps accumulating​
At the mercy of an endless love​
I detest love​
I detest ​​love​
.​
I did my best​
​​Past that selfishness that nothing​
​ Past that selfishness that nothing ​​
​​ can be done about​
​ can be done about ​​
.​
​ Lies a riddle ​​
​ Lies a riddle ​​
​ of evil love ​​
​ of evil love ​​
​ ​ Are you angry?​
​ Are you angry? ​​
​ I’m not angry ​​
​​ I’m not angry​
​ I'm not angry ​​
​​ I’m not angry​
​ I’m not angry ​​
We’re perfectly in sync​
and yet off the beat​
If this were a movie or a TV show​
Though I’d endure it until the credits​
I wouldn’t want​
to watch it again​
It’s all too cruel, from beginning​
to middle​
to end​
It’s all too cruel, from beginning​
to middle​
to end​
It’s all too cruel, from beginning​
to middle​
to end​
But​
It’s all too cruel, from beginning​
to middle​
to end​
But​
It’s all too cruel, from beginning​
to middle​
to end​
But​
It’s all too cruel, from beginning​
to middle​
to end​
But​
It’s all too cruel, from beginning​
to middle​
to end​
But​
It’s all too cruel, from beginning​
to middle​
to end​
But​
It’s all too cruel, from beginning​
to middle​
to end​
But​
It’s all too cruel, from beginning​
to middle​
to end​
But​
I still end up believing in​
a love that’s “just fine”​
So this is​
Alias:​
Love​
Target​
Age​
The topography I protected​
by hating love​
Is beginning​
to warp properly​
Isn’t it the worst?​
Like an​
interpersonal​
lotion​
We'll hurt ​​each other​
We’ll hurt each other​
over and over​
A blended love philosophy​
But​
I end up​
remembering​
the lie of​
But​
I end up​
remembering​
the lie of​
“I’m just fine”​
So​
So the​
Delusion​
Sentiment​
Compensation​
Federation​
Embraced love and​
shouted out their ideals​
A melody of fools​
with nowhere to go​
Retrying​
Rebirth​
Teleportation​
The number of tries keeps accumulating​
The number of tries keeps accumul​​ating​
The number of tries keeps ac​​cumulating​
At the mercy of an endless love​
The number of tries ke​​eps accumulating​
The number of tri​​es keeps accumulating​
At the mercy of an endless love​
The numbe​​r of tries keeps accumulating​
Alias:​
Love​
Target​
Age​
The topography​
I protected​
by hating​
The topography​
I protected​
by hating​
The topography​
I protected​
by hating​
love​
Is beginning​
to warp properly​
Isn’t it the worst?​
It’s like an​
interpersonal lotion​
We’ll hurt​
each other​
over​
and over​
A blended​
love philosophy​
I detest love​