In a village in an unknown era,​
There lived an unknown boy;​
Known to none,​
this is his fairy tale.​
Since the time I was born I was treated as a demon child;​
I received more punishment than I deserved​
I've never had anything​
to be sad about​
But into the sunset,​
I was led away​
I don't know,
​                   ​I don't know,​
I​
​​ ​​ ​don't know anythitf​
​​  ​do​​n't know anythitf​
I​
​​  ​don'​​t know anythitf​
​​  ​don't ​​know anythitf​
I​
​​  ​don't kn​​ow anythitf​
​​  ​don't know ​​anythitf​
I​
​​  ​don't know an​​ythitf​
​​  ​don't know anyt​​hitf​
I​
​​  ​don't know anythi​​tf​
I
​  ​don't know anything​
J​​even of kindness​
​after a scolding​
Not ev​​en of kindness​
Not even ​​of kindness​
​after a scolding​
Not even of ​​kindness​
Not even of kind​​ness​
​after a scolding​
Not even of kindness​
after a scolding​
​af​​ter a scolding​
Not even of kindness​
​after ​​a scolding​
​after a ​​scolding​
Not even of kindness​
​after a S​​ding​
Not even of kindness
after a scolB​
after a scolding​
Not even of kindness
e​​don't know the warmth of​
​​                  ​someone's hand after the rain​
I don't ​​know the warmth of​
I don't E​​the warmth of​
​​                  ​someone's hand after the rain​
I don't know U​​warmth of​
I don't know the warmth ​​of​
​​                  ​someone's hand after the rain​
I don't know the warmth n​​​                  ​someone's hand after the rain​
I don't know the warmth of​
​​                  ​someone's ​​hand after the rain​
​​                  ​someone's N​​after the rain​
I don't know the warmth of​
​​                  ​someone's hand after ​​the rain​
​​                  ​someone's hand after the ​​rain​
I don't know the warmth of
​                  ​someone's hand after the F​
​                  ​someone's hand after the rain​
I don't know the warmth of
H​​I'm truly, truly, truly, truly cold​
Yet ​​I'm truly, truly, truly, truly cold​
Yet h​​truly, truly, truly, truly cold​
Yet I'm ​​truly, truly, truly, truly cold​
Yet I'm tru​​ly, truly, truly, truly cold​
Yet I'm truY​​truly, truly, truly cold​
Yet I'm truly, ​​truly, truly, truly cold​
Yet I'm truly, y​​ly, truly, truly cold​
Yet I'm truly, truI​​truly, truly cold​
Yet I'm truly, truly, ​​truly, truly cold​
Yet I'm truly, truly, tru​​ly, truly cold​
Yet I'm truly, truly, truq​​truly cold​
Yet I'm truly, truly, truly, ​​truly cold​
Yet I'm truly, truly, truly, i​​ly cold​
Yet I'm truly, truly, truly, truly ​​cold​
Yet I'm truly, truly, truly, truly I​
Yet I'm truly, truly, truly, truly cold​
I won't die​
wh​​y is ​it ​I ​won't ​die?​
why ​​is it I won't die?​
why i​​s it I won't die?​
why is​​ it I won't die?​
n​​not even​
​​        ​dreaming a single dream​
I'm ​​not even​
I'm F​​even​
​​        ​dreaming a single dream​
I'm not n​​en​
I'm not evw​​​dreaming a single dream​
I'm not even​
​​        ​dre​​aming a single dream​
​​        ​dreW​​ing a single dream​
I'm not even​
​​        ​dream​​ing a single dream​
​​        ​dreamN​​a single dream​
I'm not even​
​​        ​dreaming w​​single dream​
​​        ​dreaming a f​​gle dream​
I'm not even​
​​        ​dreaming a sinO​​dream​
​​        ​dreaming a single X​​am​
I'm not even
​        ​dreaming a single dreg​
​        ​dreaming a single dream​
I'm not even
X​​so this fairy​
X​​le known to none​
And h​​this fairy​
tah​​known to none​
And so p​​is fairy​
tale kn​​own to none​
tale knh​​to none​
And so thY​​fairy​
tale known P​​none​
And so this H​​ry​
tale known to no​​ne​
And so this faiq​
tale known to noP​
And so this fairy​
tale known to none​
Was sucked up into the sunset
​                   ​and vanished into the air​
In my life of sickening violence​
and endless scorn,​
without noticing,​
you were standing there​
You were forbidden to converse with me, but​
"I want to know your name"​
Sorry, but I have no name​
and no tongue​
There is no place in the world​
where I could belong, and yet​
"Let's leave together..."​
You led me away​
I don't know,
​                   ​I don't know,​
I​
​​ ​​ ​don't know anythitf​
​​  ​do​​n't know anythitf​
I​
​​  ​don'​​t know anythitf​
​​  ​don't ​​know anythitf​
I​
​​  ​don't kn​​ow anythitf​
​​  ​don't know ​​anythitf​
I​
​​  ​don't know an​​ythitf​
​​  ​don't know anyt​​hitf​
I​
​​  ​don't know anythi​​tf​
I
​  ​don't know anything​
m​​even that​
​​    ​you're not a child anymore​
Not v​​that​
Not even E​​​you're not a child anymore​
Not even that​
​​    ⌍​​'re not a child anymore​
​​    ​you're ​​not a child anymore​
Not even that​
​​    ​you're n​​a child anymore​
​​    ​you're not a ​​child anymore​
Not even that​
​​    ​you're not a ch​​ild anymore​
​​    ​you're not a chf​​anymore​
Not even that​
​​    ​you're not a child any​​more​
Not even that
​    ​you're not a child anyF​
​    ​you're not a child anymore​
Not even that
Or the warmth of a stranger's hand​
T​​really, really, really, the real thing​
That's ​​really, really, really, the real thing​
That's real​​ly, really, really, the real thing​
That's realc​​really, really, the real thing​
That's really, ​​really, really, the real thing​
That's really, D​​ly, really, the real thing​
That's really, realT​​really, the real thing​
That's really, really, ​​really, the real thing​
That's really, really, l​​ly, the real thing​
That's really, really, realt​​the real thing​
That's really, really, really, ​​the real thing​
That's really, really, really, M​​real thing​
That's really, really, really, the real thi​​ng​
That's really, really, really, the real thim​
That's really, really, really, the real thing​
You won't stop​
wh​​y ​won't ​you ​st​op​?​
why w​​on't you stop?​
I​​you're found out,​
​​    ​you know you shall be killed​
If q​​'re found out,​
If you⌞​​found out,​
​​    ​you know you shall be killed​
If you're I​​und out,​
If you're foR​​out,​
​​    ​you know you shall be killed​
If you're found b​​​you know you shall be killed​
If you're found out,​
​​    ⌑​​know you shall be killed​
​​    ​you a​​you shall be killed​
If you're found out,​
​​    ​you know i​​shall be killed​
​​    ​you know you R​​all be killed​
If you're found out,​
​​    ​you know you shB​​be killed​
​​    ​you know you shall j​​killed​
If you're found out,​
​​    ​you know you shall be s​​ed​
If you're found out,
​    ​you know you shall be killB​
​    ​you know you shall be killed​
If you're found out,
⎱​​After the rain,​
s​​re stood two forsaken​
​​​C​ter the rain,​
theC​​stood two forsaken​
​​​AfL​the rain,​
there L​​od two forsaken​
​​​After t​rain,​
there stood ​​two forsaken​
there stood l​​forsaken​
​​​After the d​in,​
there stood two t​​saken​
​​​After the raL​,​
there stood two forsa​​ken​
​​​After the rain⌕​
there stood two forsaU​
​​​After the rain,​
there stood two forsaken​
To be sucked up into the sunset
​                   ​and to vanish into the air​
The sun ​​goes down,      ​the dawn ​breaks,​
We play ​​to exhaustion,      ​we catch each other​
If this world could just be me and you​
If only everyone else could just be gone​
If only ​​everyone else could just be gone​
If only ​​everyone else ​could just be gone​
If only everyone else ​​could just be gone​
If only everyone else could just be gone​
I don't know, I don't know, but I heard a voice,​
Not mine or yours,​
but all humanity's​
With no chance to resist, I was led away​
With ​​no ​chance ​to ​resist, ​I ​was ​led ​away​
T​​be sucked up into the sunset, and vanish into the air​
To be ​​sucked up into the sunset, and vanish into the air​
To be su​​cked up into the sunset, and vanish into the air​
To be suck​​ed up into the sunset, and vanish into the air​
To be sucked ​​up into the sunset, and vanish into the air​
To be sucked up ​​into the sunset, and vanish into the air​
To be sucked up in​​to the sunset, and vanish into the air​
To be sucked up inD​​the sunset, and vanish into the air​
To be sucked up into the ​​sunset, and vanish into the air​
To be sucked up into the sun​​set, and vanish into the air​
To be sucked up into the sunD​​and vanish into the air​
To be sucked up into the sunset, and ​​vanish into the air​
To be sucked up into the sunset, and va​​nish into the air​
To be sucked up into the sunset, and vani​​sh into the air​
To be sucked up into the sunset, and vanim​​into the air​
To be sucked up into the sunset, and vanish in​​to the air​
To be sucked up into the sunset, and vanish inu​​ the air​
To be sucked up into the sunset, and vanish into the ​​air​
To be sucked up into the sunset, and vanish into the U​
To be sucked up into the sunset, and vanish into the air​
X​​don't know, I don't know,​
I don't ​​know, I don't know,​
I don't x​​I don't know,​
I don't know, ​​I don't know,​
I don't know, I ​​don't know,​
I don't know, I X​​know,​
I don't know, I don't H​
I don't know, I don't know,​
H​​don't know anything​
I P​​'t know anything​
I don⏜​​know anything​
I don't h​​anything​
I don't know ​​anything​
I don't know I​​thing​
I don't know anyr​​ng​
I don't know anythia​
I don't know anything​
Wh​​at ​wi​ll ​hap​pen ​ne​xt, ​or ​your ​na​me​
But even right now, I think this will do​
P​​truly, truly, truly,​
That's ​​truly, truly, truly,​
That's h​​ly, truly, truly,​
That's truQ​​truly, truly,​
That's truly, ​​truly, truly,​
That's truly, y​​ly, truly,​
That's truly, trui​​truly,​
That's truly, truly, tru​​ly,​
That's truly, truly, truq​
That's truly, truly, truly,​
Y​​ly what I think​
tru​​ly what I think​
trua​​what I think​
truly ​​what I think​
truly i​​I think​
truly what Q​​think​
truly what I ​​think​
truly what I r​
truly what I think​
j​​don't know, I don't know,​
I ​​don't know, I don't know,​
I J​​know, I don't know,​
I don't ​​know, I don't know,​
I don't k​​I don't know,​
I don't know, ​​I don't know,​
I don't know, S​​don't know,​
I don't know, I C​​know,​
I don't know, I don't k​
I don't know, I don't know,​
but the buzzing in my ears​
O​​sucked up into the sunset, and vanished into the air​
Was ​​sucked up into the sunset, and vanished into the air​
Was p​​ed up into the sunset, and vanished into the air​
Was suckX​​up into the sunset, and vanished into the air​
Was sucked H​​into the sunset, and vanished into the air​
Was sucked up ​​into the sunset, and vanished into the air​
Was sucked up h​​to the sunset, and vanished into the air​
Was sucked up in​​to the sunset, and vanished into the air​
Was sucked up inh​​the sunset, and vanished into the air​
Was sucked up into ​​the sunset, and vanished into the air​
Was sucked up into X​​sunset, and vanished into the air​
Was sucked up into the ​​sunset, and vanished into the air​
Was sucked up into the y​​set, and vanished into the air​
Was sucked up into the sunh​​and vanished into the air​
Was sucked up into the sunset, Q​​vanished into the air​
Was sucked up into the sunset, and Y​​ished into the air​
Was sucked up into the sunset, and van​​ished into the air​
Was sucked up into the sunset, and vanH​​ed into the air​
Was sucked up into the sunset, and vanishq​​into the air​
Was sucked up into the sunset, and vanished ​​into the air​
Was sucked up into the sunset, and vanished I​​to the air​
Was sucked up into the sunset, and vanished inr​​the air​
Was sucked up into the sunset, and vanished into a​​air​
Was sucked up into the sunset, and vanished into the ​​air​
Was sucked up into the sunset, and vanished into the R​
Was sucked up into the sunset, and vanished into the air​
K​​titles: Shonver​
subb​​tles: Shonver​
subtiJ​​Shonver​
subtitles: ​​Shonver​
subtitles: J​​onver​
subtitles: Shs​​ver​
subtitles: Shon​​ver​
subtitles: ShonT​
subtitles: Shonver​
​​